# **Web Developer**



# Shimul Shil



42347239



shimul\_ustc@yahoo.com



Rebæk Søpark 25, 3TV 2650 Hvidovre www.linkedin.com/in/shimul-shil



Date of Birth - 1980

#### **Professional Skills**

- HTML
- CSS/Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- PHP
- React
- Angular
- MySQL

# **Knowledge On**

- Unity
- Ionic-5
- Photoshop
- React-360
- Figma
- UX Design

### **Professional Profile**

I'm a Web developer who loves building user-friendly websites and web apps. I've an experience to developed consumer focused websites by using HTML-5, CSS, PHP, React, Bootstrap, Foundation, Angular and JavaScript. Most recently, I've been building websites with React and PHP. I'm currently interested in learning more Bootstrap and delving deeper into React & PHP. Designed and developed web applications across multiple APIs and MySQL Databases. Ability self-manage independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

My greatest strength is my quickest learning capability and adapt to new situations, configurations and technologies.

### Personal competence

- Initiative
- Team work
- Curious & Helpful
- Analytical and organizing
- Problem Solving

- Responsibility
- · Strong in decision making
- Planning of work assignments
- Strong communicator
- Focusing on deadlines

### **Education**

Top-up Bachelor's degree - Web Development Zealand Institute of Business and Technology, Roskilde, Denmark. <a href="https://zealand.com/">https://zealand.com/</a>

February -2021 - Ongoing

**Vocational Web Developer** 

Roskilde Tekniske Skole, Roskilde, Denmark.

https://www.rts.dk/

August 2020- January-2021 (Grundforløbets -2)

Masters in Electrical Engineering (Telecommunication), Blekinge Institute of Technology, Sweden.

https://www.bth.se/eng/

October 2008- December 2010

Bachelor in Computer Science & Engineering, University of Science & Technology Chittagong, Bangladesh. https://www.ustc.ac.bd/

January 2001- December 2005

# **Institutional Project Works**

**Mental Shower- Semester project** 

https://mentalshower.mi-designstudio.com/selection Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Ionic-5 & Angular

Individual-Project-

https://individual-project.netlify.app
Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

## Language Skills

- English Fluent in all aspect
- Bengali Native
- Danish Intermediate

### **Aktivities/Volunteering**

Active member of event organizing and leadership committee of Bengali Cultural Association (BCAS) from 2013.

Member of Non-profit Organization UNICEF as a financial supporter from 2014, to saves children's lives, defends their rights, and helps them fulfill their potential.

### **Driving License**

Category-B

#### Interests

- Travelling
- Social work
- Playing Badminton
- Playing Football
- Long driving
- Camping

### **Individual-Project-Shop**

https://sko-butik-project.netlify.app
Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

#### Dice- Game -

https://dice-game-project.netlify.app/ Using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & PHP

#### RTS-uw-uddennelser-

https://rts-uw-uddennelser.netlify.app
Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

### The Band- Project

https://the-band-opgaver.netlify.app
Using HTML, CSS & JavaScript

# **Work Experience**

**Team Member- DHL Aviation.** 

Kastrup, Denmark.

December 2015- September 2019.

Service Assistant, Børne-og-Ungdemsforvaltningen. Copenhagen Kommune, Denmark.

April 2014 - April 2016

Freelance IT-Supporter, Shetty Foundation.

Chittagong, Bangladesh.

December 2010- July 2012

Network Support Executive, Worldye Dress Pants ltd. Chittagong, Bangladesh.

June 2006 - July 2008

Network Support , Ichinet Ltd, CTG, Bangladesh.

Chittagong, Bangladesh.

October 2005-May 2006